Hello Darkness, my new friend.
Orion and the Dark is a animation, family, comedy
film directed by Sean Charmatz.
A boy with an active imagination faces his fears on an unforgettable journey through
the night with his new friend: a giant, smiling creature named Dark.
Orion (voice), played by Jacob Tremblay.
Dark (voice), played by Paul Walter Hauser.
Sweet Dreams (voice), played by Angela Bassett.
Adult Orion (voice), played by Colin Hanks.
Sleep (voice), played by Natasia Demetriou.
Unexplained Noises (voice), played by Golda Rosheuvel.
Orion and the Dark is a 2024 American animated fantasy adventure film
written by Charlie Kaufman and directed by Sean Charmatz.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation for Netflix, it is based on the 2014
children's book Orion and the Dark by Emma Yarlett.
The film stars Jacob Tremblay and Paul Walter Hauser as the titular characters, alongside the voices of Colin Hanks, Mia Akemi Brown, Ike
Barinholtz, Nat Faxon, Golda Rosheuvel, Natasia Demetriou, Aparna Nancherla, Carla Gugino, Matt Dellapina, and Angela Bassett.
Robert Lydecker and Kevin Lax composed the film's musical score.
Orion and the Dark premiered at the TUDUM Theater in Los Angeles on
January 27, 2024, and was released on Netflix on February 2.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of underdog, cat, fear, based
on children's book, fear of the dark.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.